{
    "id": "8f9f1db60a3146128c872f27b1457db3",
    "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I ……………………… about your problems, I would have helped you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8b133cd5b5c6488eab79338a1a079077"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has agreed to ……………………….. my dogs while I am away on holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look for",
                "look after",
                "look at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59e393cec2be49bd891ba67d6a5dcd20"
        },
        {
            "question": "They made the child ………………………. the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "drinking",
                "to drink"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1d8318e1b7d4dee8abf0a014781de84"
        },
        {
            "question": "She makes her children ……………………………… their lessons everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "learn",
                "to learn",
                "learning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b9831a0505f4d60b839c7d16840de1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The test was …………………… .. difficult that she couldn’t answer many questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04c2979888a1468eaef7f118e73e3fed"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. this work by next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will finish",
                "would finish",
                "will have finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "982865a3603a460e85ecec736d1bd549"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… by the time we arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4096a3f0556479f8244ebf59312edc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I stopped …………………….. to him, he was working in his garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "speaking",
                "to speak"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3eaca8065db74c3eb9495916456d42a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Despite ……………………. hard, he failed the exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "working",
                "to work"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64c53ef54bd64e53af2a17def46bad37"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. play a lot of tennis when he was young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "did used to",
                "was used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09c6d76d9555490f83e51003f7830c86"
        }
    ]
}